Okay so now we're going to look at the eyes, nose and mouth, start with the mouth, highest amount of contrast in there.
Top lip, well that's the middle is ring, maybe a touch of purple in there, maybe a tone that down with a touch of green.
Chrome is too high. Okay, bottom lip, got something in the middle is ring, right in the middle is ring,
touch of mid-green if you want to tone that down, too grey, middle is ring, touch of mid-red.
Just look at that, you can always change these, take this chroma down after, you're right up to the edge.
Okay so that's the lip, so then we'll look at the nose, bouncing the eyes, okay nose again,
got a bit of yellow in there, red, illiterate, green, so some light red, illiterate, yellow.
Just test that with the tone, red darker, which is green, edge of it, just look around there,
there are the brow, green, touch of the nose, that's a bit dark so you can see, all of the nose.
Okay so that's the nose, okay, look at the eye.
Okay so start with the eyelids, something between a lighter and mid red, some yellow, so green, illiterate, check it,
I'll go with something like that, it's got to be darker in some places lighter than others, a bit more green in there, darker.
Then rest the eyes, a bit more on the greenish side, a bit more green yellow to the red,
test that first, more green, more yellow, okay so I'm going to go with something like that,
got to soften this edge, a bit lighter colour there, okay, other eye, same,
another nose and mouth, don't look at the ear, just soften this a bit.
Okay let's look at the ear, quite kind of neutral, not very red, so maybe just a lighter version of this,
maybe a touch of red in there, so some yellow, so just mix that yellow into this red,
just put a bit of close to that, a bit darker, such a green, put that down a bit,
so I'm just making this slightly darker, can always pick out the lights after the edges,
okay, more on the green side actually, more neutral, get some more green,
a bit more yellow into that, more green, just more yellow.
Then you get slightly darker on the emissary, more chroma, more green on the red side,
that one is one really but, okay so that's the eyes, nose and mouth shape,
going to bring that back to the violet, so here's some yellow, just looking at that shadow,
a bit more main, orange, just to bring this back, can't see that,
actually a bit warmer, a bit more red, a bit better, okay, nose and mouth shape, okay.